

## **Baran Buket Yıldız**

O Home: Çankaya, 06530, Ankara, Türkiye

**Email:** <u>baranbuket12@gmail.com</u> **Phone:** (+90) 5301779632

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/baran-buket-yıldız-19a1a2202

Github: <a href="https://github.com/BaranBuketYildiz">https://github.com/BaranBuketYildiz</a>

**Gender:** Female **Date of birth:** 28/01/1999 **Nationality:** Turkish

#### **ABOUT ME**

My name is Baran Buket and I recently graduated with a Bachelor's degree in Computer Engineering from Baskent University. Along my academic life, I gained solid information in various areas of computer engineering, including web development, mobil development, algorithms.. I want to improve my knowledge about i am related areas and gain different experiences The desire and feeling to always add something to myself drives me further on this path even more determinedly. I am an engineer candidate who is always ready and enthusiastic to learn new technologies. Thank you for your time and consideration.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

[ 03/07/2023 - 01/09/2023 ]

## **Computer Engineering (Intern)**

#### B.E.A.R TELL

City: Ankara Country: Türkiye

- Research and development various NLP (National Language Processing) tasks such as question answering, summarization and translation.
- An Al based chatbot was developed and deployed. React and Keycloak were used for frontend, Flask, PostgreSQL and ChromaDB were preferred for backend.
- Python libraries such as LlamaIndex and Langchain were used for the Al side.

# [ 10/08/2022 - 12/09/2022 ] **Computer Engineering ( Intern)**

## National Internship Program

City: Karabük Country: Türkiye Web developer

## **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

## $[\ 09/2018 - 06/2023\ ]$ Computer Engineering Baskent University

City: Ankara Country: Türkiye

#### LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Turkish

Other language(s):

### **English**

LISTENING B2 READING B2 WRITING B2

**SPOKEN PRODUCTION B1 SPOKEN INTERACTION B1** 

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

#### **DIGITAL SKILLS**

Javascript | Java | HTML & CSS | Node.Js, React.Js | Flutter | PostgreSQL | Python Flask (intermediate) | Node.js | Pyhton | C++ | MySQL

